### BRYAN TONG

btong@berkeley.edu
bryantong@outlook.com
+1 (925) 577-6826

STUDENT / ENTREPRENEUR

#### Summary

A creative, ambitious student and entrepreneur with an interest in consumer technology, business, and law. Currently studying Cognitive Science with an intended double major in Legal Studies at University of California, Berkeley. Possesses realworld business experience as the former CEO of MIRAI Apparel; holds an additional 6 years' experience in UI/UX, contracting, and marketing.

#### Experience

# **Cryptocom.pw**Lead Graphic Designer

2014 – 2015 Palo Alto, CA Daily

Interim Lead Graphic Designer of CryptoCom.pw, a Palo Alto based telecommunications and mobile encryption startup. Focused on directing a vision for front-end UX and corporate branding. Collaborated with engineers in 3D printing components.

## MIRAI Apparel Chief Executive Officer

2012 – 2015 Pleasanton, CA Full-time

Designed high-end clothing, primarily of urban/streetwear styles. Worked with American Apparel and local screen printers to produce entirely American manufactured apparel. Oversaw all aspects of the company, ranging from product design, website code, and school marketing teams. With launch of first product line, local and viral marketing generated brand recognition by tens of thousands of individuals and generating profit of high thousands within weeks of first product sales.

### Experience (cont.)

## Interact / Rotary Board Member

2012 – 2015 Foothill High Weekly

Aided in recruiting new members to Interact's Division 5170. Encouraged peers to meet new people, volunteer for various events, and organized spirit events within Interact. Additionally, performed behind-the-scenes management for charity dinners and auctions.

# Amnesty International Historian

2013 – 2014 Foothill High Weekly

Documented club activities, engaged members in participation of club-held events and speeches. Helped organized events with other club leaders that appeared on local news.

#### Education

University of California, Berkeley Bachelor's Degree, Cognitive Science Bachelor's Degree, Legal Studies 2015 - 2019